

Breanna DeNino

Scottsdale, AZ 85260 4802701374 brdenino@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL **SUMMARY**

Learning leader with over 10 years of experience who finds joy in helping others and the company succeed. Helps participants obtain the knowledge and skills they need to thrive in a fast-paced setting. Develops interpersonal skills while offering a complete and thorough lesson plan. Offers prompt constructive feedback on training assessments, participant performance and overall effectiveness of each training session. Driven to learn more about machine learning and it's impact with in the learning and development world.

SKILLS

- Charismatic public speaker
- Project management
- Intuitive people management skills
- Tailoring curriculum plans
- Positive learning environment
- A passion for continuous learning
- A problem solver and action oriented
- Managing classroom for diverse populations
- Strong and credible leadership mentor

WORK HISTORY

FINANCIAL OPERATIONS TRAINING MANAGER

03/2022 to CURRENT

SnapCare | Scottsdale, AZ

- Coordinated technical training and personal development classes for team members at all levels.
- Build comprehensive training materials and clinician user guides. Created an internal knowledge base, shared across various departments enhancing overall operational efficiency.
- Streamlining the new clinician onboarding process and ensuring a smooth transition into SnapCare.
- Directed training programs and development paths for managers and supervisors.
- Led organizational training and process documentation launching Salesforce while deprecating Zendesk.
- Planned and monitored the implementation of Bridge which is a technology-based LMS.
- Developed and implemented a comprehensive training program to increase employee productivity and skill development.

SENIOR LEARNING MANAGER

10/2021 to 02/2022

Arizona Society Of CPAs | Phoenix, AZ

Developed departmental systems and procedures to better align workflow processes.

- Directed field training to enhance participants' skills.
- Managed all exempt employee coaching, training and performance improvement actions.
- Trained staff during demonstrations, meetings, conferences and workshops.

LEARNING AND DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST

06/2018 to 10/2021

Plexus Worldwide | Scottsdale, AZ

- Design and develop creative, learner-centered, performance-based training materials in multiple modalities including classroom, job aids, facilitator guides, and participant guides for over 500 internal and vendor team members
- Develops training and faculty development programs by researching topics, viewing and evaluating content materials, and making recommendations. Applies best practices in teaching, instructional design using Kirkpatricks 4 Types of Evaluation, and 70/20/10 model of learning
- Certify vendor trainers and ensure best practices are used adhering to training KPI and curriculum
- Implement Litmos (LMS) and EmpowerU(LMS), with a focus on ease of access and blended learning model
- Develop leadership development curriculum for leaders and managers across various levels that includes Franklin Covey's 6 Critical Practices of Leading a Team, Leading at the Speed of Trust and Speed of Trust, InsideOut Coaching, and Presentation Advantage
- Partner cross-functionally to deliver cohesive core and functional training plans for specific roles
- Assess individual department learning needs and develop quality interactive training documents and/or blended learning outcomes (such as eLearning, and videos) for company-wide implementation
- Measure results of learning and development programs to demonstrate iROI
- Deliver systems, product and process training using a variety of delivery methods to keep classes fully engaged
- Let organizational training and documentation for Zendesk Help Center, Chat and Support.

LEARNING AND PERFORMANCE TRAINER

08/2017 to 06/2018

Ring | Mesa, AZ

- Assist training leadership in the development of new/future training processes for continuing education
- Provides training surveys to new hires for feedback and review for areas of improvement
- Performs other assignments or projects as requested by Training Manager and SupervisorDeveloping effective new hire programmes

- Working knowledge of Adult Learning theories such as pedagogy and andragogy
- Researching new methodologies in workplace learning and presenting this research
- Manage, process, and review timesheets, payroll, and daily attendance of new hires
- Developed and delivered Exceptional Service training program
- Lead and/or attend meetings and cross-functional teams for diverse policy and process improvements

TRAINER 01/2015 to 01/2017

Revana | Tempe, AZ

- Facilitate Training Programs for up to 30+ employees
- Used program analysis to identify training needs by closely working with Marketing and Managers
- Conducted 1-1 weekly meetings in new hire training and in nesting
- Created 30, 60, 90-day training calendars
- Facilitated weekly Closed-Loop meetings with Talent Acquisition, Human Capital, Operations Director, Training Director and Training Manager
- Soley responsible for training multiple sales, chat and lead gen programs such as Angie's List, Verizon, and Intuit
- Implemented standard operation procedures requested by Nissan
- Intuit training class influence \$120,000 in revenue
- Assisted in the development and facilitation of Advance! program
- March Platinum Club winner
- Develop facilitator, participant and training materials for multiple products

OPERATIONS TRAINER

03/2009 to 09/2015

Alorica | Mesa, AZ

EDUCATION (

Coding Bootcamp

EXPECTED IN 02/2024

Arizona State University, Tempe, AZ

Certified Scrum Master

09/2022

Scrum Alliance

Information Mapping Certification

2021

Information Mapping

Management And Strategy Institute

2019

Six Sigma Black Belt Professional (SSBBP) License ID: 25163054

Management And Strategy Institute Certified Team Supervisor License ID: 27375583	2019
Real Colors Facilitator Certification National Curriculum And Training Institute	2019
InsideOut Coaching Presenter Certification InsideOut Development	2018
Six Sigma Global Institute Six Sigma Lean Green Belt (LGBC)	2018